http://www.businessrecord.com/Content/Default/Default/Article/Privacy-policy/-3/-3/83179

Search only accepts letters and numbers.
Home | Advertising | Membership | Newsletters | Contact Us | About | BPC News | Submit Releases | Log Out
PREVIOUS ISSUESNEWS BY INDUSTRY
CoronavirusAll Latest NewsBanking & FinanceBPC News ReleasesBusiness Community EventsBusiness Record E-newslettersBusiness Record Insider CultureEconomic DevelopmentEnergy & EnvironmentHealth & WellnessHR & EducationInsurance & InvestmentsIowa NewsIowa Stops HungerLaw & GovernmentLift IOWAManufacturing & LogisticsOn The MoveOn the RecordOpinionReal Estate & DevelopmentRetail & BusinessSales & MarketingTech & InnovationThe Insider NotebookTransportation
SPECIALTY PRODUCTS
Annual Real Estate MagazineBest of Des Moines Book of ListsBPC Book PublishingBusiness InsightsCustom PublishingDevelopment Guides Fearless e-newsletterGreaterinnovationIOWAIowa Stops HungerMade in IowaNewcomer's GuidePillars of PhilanthropySpecial Advertising SectionsMade in Iowa
EVENTS
Buy TicketsUpcoming Business Record EventsFearless LaunchBook of Lists Unveiling PartyPower BreakfastinnovationIOWA unveilingWomen of InfluenceEconomic ForecastCommercial Real Estate ForumForty Under 4090 ideas in 90 minutes
AWARDS
HR Exec. of the YearForty Under 40Forty Under 40 AlumnusCRE Pro of the YearInnovationIOWA AwardsWomen of InfluenceCFO of the Year
CALENDAREXECUTIVE TOOLS
Public NoticesReprints of Business RecordRequest Rate CardRSS FeedsVideo
Privacy policy
Sunday, July 1, 2018 12:00 AM
Business Publications Corporation Inc. (BPC) is committed to
protecting your privacy. We will only process your personal data in the manner
and purpose for which we collect it, for the purposes you later authorize, or
as outlined here.
We are committed to using third-party vendors who also
comply with these rules and are also committed to protecting your privacy. Both
BPC and our contracted vendors will maintain reasonable procedures to help
ensure that personal data we collect and use is reliable for its intended use
and is accurate, complete and current. If your data is transferred to any third-party
vendor we hire, it is limited to the express use for BPC and not for any of
those vendors’ use or for their resale to other entities.
Acceptable use by BPC pursuant to this policy includes follow-up contacts regarding a purchase or event registration you've made with us, future marketing opportunities for BPC, sharing of event registration data with event sponsors for their use and inclusion of data received for inclusion on targeted electronic newsletters pertaining to topics of interest.
All subscription lists -- both for print publications and
electronic newsletters -- are the sole property of BPC and are not resold for any
external use.
You have the right to change or delete information we have
on file for you. Requests should be made through circulation@bpcdm.com or by calling
515.288.3338, extension 201. For email correspondence, use the unsubscribe
mechanism built-in at the bottom of each message.
General inquiries can be made by contacting:
Business Publications Corporation Inc.
Attn:  Privacy Policy
100 4th Street
Des Moines, IA 50309
X
Most ViewedMost Commented
$250 million multi-use development planned for Grimes
NOTABLE TRANSACTIONS: Mall group buys former Merle Hay Sears property
Des Moines’ Davis Brown Law Firm combining with Dentons
Argonne Building's $7.25 million renovation nearing completion; tenants will begin moving in soon
Catch of day: Is Iowa poised to be leader in seafood production?
Home | Advertising | Membership | Newsletters | Contact Us | About | BPC News | Submit Releases | Log Out
Facebook
Twitter
RSS
The Depot at 4th, 100 4th Street, Des Moines, Iowa 50309 | (515) 288-3336 | © 2020 Business Record. All Rights Reserved. | Legal disclaimer | Privacy Policy
Software © 2020 1up! Software, All Rights Reserved
{1}
##LOC[OK]##
{1}
##LOC[OK]##
##LOC[Cancel]##
{1}
##LOC[OK]##
